diinoweb.com 2013-04-29

# Privacy Policy

(by registering or using the services or the site you agree to processing of your personal data in accordance with the terms and conditions in the Privacy Policy) (by providing your personal data you agree to processing of your personal data in accordance with the terms and conditions in the Privacy Policy)

**We are committed to protecting your privacy.**

The Privacy Policy is created to respect and protect the privacy of our users. It is consistent with the standards of the industry, to ensure security, integrity and privacy of information collected from individuals.

This Privacy Policy applies to the collection, use and disclosure of all personal data that may be obtained by Diino AB and, when applicable, other companies within the Diino group of companies (“Diino”), at anytime you interact with us. Personal data may for example be collected when you visit our websites, sign-up for products, purchase products or participate in any marketing activities.

The data collected by Diino may be stored and processed in any country in which Diino operates. You also consent to any such transfer of your personal data to a country outside the European Union or to a state not member of the European Economic Area. Should such a transfer take place, the information remains subject to this Privacy Policy. Diino abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.

**Personal Data usage**  
Diino use your personal data in order to perform the relevant assignment, or to confirm your identity, maintain your personal profile and to manage and administer the products and services provided to you. Further, Diino processes personal data in order to deliver tailored services to our customers, such as product and services offerings, software updates, newsletters and support. In addition the information gathered will help us determine how to improve our services and make them even better.

If you use the Service under a [free account] Diino may allow third parties to advertise in the Service and may let third parties to advertise through e-mail to you. You may at any time withdraw you consent to receive advertising through e-mail.

Diino may also collect demographic data, such as preferences, interests, age, and geographic information in order to analyze and tailor the services provided.  
Diino may record and monitor your IP address for system administration and for fraud prevention purposes. IP Addresses are not linked or cross-referenced with any personally identifiable information.

**Data Collection**  
Diino provides customers with an online service, which can be used to store, access, share and publish digital files. Accessing the Diino account requires unique identification. To establish an identifiable profile we require a first name, last name, password, country, and a valid e-mail address.

The user accounts are password protected in order to secure the information you have stored. We require that you do not reveal the account information to anyone.

Standard free Diino account: Diino requires your name and your email address when registering for a standard free account.

Account upgrade: If you decide to upgrade your Diino account and become a paying customer our billing supplier will require additional information, such as your credit card number and address. Diino does not store credit card information.

**Disclosure**  
Diino takes your privacy seriously, therefore we do not sell or rent your contact information to other companies, except as outlined in the Privacy Policy or in the Service Agreement.

On occasion we hire external suppliers to process transactions, mailings, customer support cases or perform statistical analysis of the website. Your personal data may be disclosed to and processed by such suppliers. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information provided and prohibited to use the data for other purposes Your personal data may also be processed by other partners of Diino, [such as providers of newsletters.]

Some of our product offerings may be co-branded in cooperation with other companies. If you register for co-branded promotions, both Diino and the other company may receive the information that has been gathered. Should you sign-up to Diino through a third party retailer or vendor the co-branded policy applies.

Diino will disclose account information in case we have indications that disclosing this information is necessary to contact, identify or bring legal action against a person, company or organization who may be violating Diino’s Service Agreement or may be causing injury to or interference with Diino AB´s rights or property (intentionally or unintentionally), other Diino users, or anyone else that could be the target or harmed by such activities.

As a user you authorize Diino to disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as Diino, in its sole discretion, believes necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, or other activity that is illegal or may expose Diino to legal liability. Diino may disclose or access account information when Diino in good faith believes that it is required by law.

**Cookies and IP addresses**  
Diino uses cookies, as many other websites, to collect information on website usage. Cookies are specific types of information that a website transfers to the user’s computer and that can later be read by the web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. The gathered information is anonymous and does not contain name, e-mail address or any other information that can be linked to a specific person. You have the ability to decline cookies by changing the settings on your browser.

**External links**  
Diino’s website may contain links to other sites. Diino cannot control and is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements on visited sites. This Privacy Policy only applies to information that is included on our websites.

**Advertising networks**  
Diino uses advertising networks to present advertisements on the website. Occasionally these advertising companies use cookies, web beacons or similar technologies to target campaigns according to usage. The information obtained is not identifiable. These advertisers are subject to their respective Private Policies.

**Merger and Acquisition**  
As Diino is in a stage of expansion of its business. Diino may sell or buy subsidiaries or business units. Should such transactions take place as well as in the event Diino or substantially all or parts of its assets are acquired by a third party, personal information of Diino users will generally be one of the transferred business assets. We reserve the right to include your personal information as well as all the information on all Diino accounts in any such transfer to a third party.

**Children**  
Diino does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 for marketing proposes. If it comes to our attention that a child under 13 submits personal information to us, we will delete the information as soon as possible.

**Waiver of Special Offers**  
Users who do not want to receive information on offers, special deals or services may choose the option of not receiving these communications by replying with unsubscribe in the subject line in the e-mail, opt-out in the client or use the unsubscribe link in the newsletters.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**  
This Privacy Policy will occasionally be updated to include any additional products. We encourage you to review this policy on a regular basis.

**Additional information**  
Diino AB, Barnhusgatan 16, 111 23 Stockholm, Sweden, is the data controller under the Swedish Personal Data Act. Please write to Diino AB if you have any questions in relation to Diino’s processing of your personal data. You may at all times request that incorrect data is revised. Diino AB will, upon your written application – with your personal signature – provide information, once a year and free of charge, on your personal data being processed, the sources from which the data have been collected, the purposes of the processing and to which recipients or categories of recipients the data has been disclosed. Diino AB is also liable upon your request to rectify, block or erase personal data that has not been processed in accordance with the Swedish Personal Data Act.

Please feel free to contact us with any questions or comments you have regarding the Privacy Policy. Email: [info@diino.com](mailto:info@diino.com). For further information about the Diino service we refer to our Service Agreement on our website.

 **  
Storing files on Diino**  
Diino provides an online service for storing and sharing files. We do not in any way disclose information on the files stored in your personal user account to other companies. The files stored under your Diino account are your property. If we are required by law or litigation to disclose personal information we will do so.

**How we secure the data**  
The data stored is secured with the help of drivers and daily back-ups. The information is stored on servers in a highly secure facility with 24 hours-a-day surveillance, EMP-security, fire protection, emergency power back-up systems, climate control and state of the art access controls. Vital hardware is robust providing you with high availability and protection from power outages, cable failures, and natural disasters.

**Transferring information over the Internet**  
To secure the transmissions over the Internet we have implemented technical, administrative and physical safeguards. The data is encrypted during transmission to and from our servers, however we cannot ensure complete security whilst transferring files over the Internet.

**Sharing files or sending files using Diino**  
Using Diino to share and send files requires stating the receiver’s email address. Diino does not use these email addresses and does not sell nor make these available to any third party. Using the Diino client to send or share a file is a function intended for one-time use only. You also have the option to generate a link to the specific file or folder and paste that in to an email directly.

**Password**  
Please, as a user, bear in mind that you yourself is responsible for not revealing your password to others. Keep your password in a safe place. Your password should consist of 5-12 characters. Also consider letting your password consist of small and capital letters, numbers and other characters mixed together to that way further constrain others from finding out your password.

 **Copyrighted materials**  
We are required by law to take down music, pictures, videos or other material uploaded to Diino if we learn that it infringes copyright regulations and laws. If any of our users upload and share copyrighted materials repeatedly we will terminate the contract with this user. If you have mistakenly uploaded or published such material, or we have taken down content that you have permission to publish please let us know. If you have reason to believe that any of our users are violating copyright laws, please contact us, likewise if your work has been copied and is accessible on Diino. [info@diino.net](mailto:info@diino.net)
